rtilive.pk 2016-11-01

# RTI LIVE, News Agency Pakistan, Right To Information Pakistan, National News Network Pakistan, RTI Pakistan, Latest news, online news Pakistan

Please know that while using this website and/or submitting information at this website you are volunteering the same; you are informed of the way such information may be used and you agree to such use.

**Privacy Policy**

The RTI LIVE shares your concerns about maintaining the integrity and privacy of personal information collected on the Internet. The RTI LIVE is committed to protecting your privacy, and the following Privacy Policy ("Policy") is intended to explain our information collection and dissemination practices in connection with the rtilive.pk web site (the "Site"). Please review the entire Policy and feel free to contact us at info@rtilive.pk if you have any questions. Also, see our Terms & Conditions for accessing the site and using the content. 

**1) Collection of Personal Information**

In order to monitor the Site's performance and for statistical and routine system maintenance purposes, the RTI LIVE may collect (a) the home server domain names, IP addresses, type of computer, and type of web browser of users of the Site ("you"), and (b) aggregate information on which pages you access. 

Beyond the above information, the RTI LIVE only collects personal information (e.g., name, email, mailing address and phone number) that you voluntarily submit to us. This information is used by the RTI LIVE or its contracted service providers solely to provide you with the information and materials you have requested, such as datasets, email updates and other materials regarding RTI LIVE and its programs. 

**2) Use of Personal Data Collected**

The RTI LIVE will not sell, share, rent or disclose to third parties any individually identifying information, such as names, postal and email addresses, telephone numbers, and other personal information which you voluntarily provide to us, except (a) to provide the services you have requested; (b) to the extent necessary to comply with applicable laws or valid legal processes, or (c) to protect the rights and intellectual property of the RTI LIVE. 

Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information, and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. 

The RTI LIVE works with a third-party vendor, Constant Contact, to provide users its email update service. All personal information obtained pursuant to RTI LIVE email subscription services is covered by Constant Contact's Email Privacy Policy. 

**3) User's Rights**

You may obtain a summary of any of your personally identifiable information retained by us, or you may modify, correct, change or update such information by contacting the RTI LIVE via the postal address, email or telephone number listed below. 

**4) Links**

The Site may contain links to other Internet web sites. However, the RTI LIVE does not endorse, and is not responsible for, the privacy practices or the content of these web sites. You should review these policies in connection with your use of such third-party sites. 

**5) Security Measures**

The RTI LIVE has established reasonable precautions to protect collected personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Please note that while the RTI LIVE has endeavored to create a secure and reliable Site for users, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from RTI LIVE via the Site or email cannot be guaranteed. 

**6) Right to Contact**

The RTI LIVE reserves the right to contact users of the Site regarding changes to this Policy, the terms of use of the Site, or any other policies, agreements or transactions relevant to Site users. 

**How We Use the Information**

The information you submit will be used by us for communication and contact, to fulfill your requests, to respond to inquiries and to offer other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you or to the person whose information you submit to us. 

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a letter to our editors, comments, a posting to a blog or a discussion board), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. 

We use the non-personally identifiable information that you submit to improve our website. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or summon. We may also disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company. Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that you submit will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy policy (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. 

**Cookies & Web Beacons**

To enhance your experience with our website, our web pages may use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use cookies to understand website usage and to improve the content and offerings on our website. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. 

"Web beacons" or clear.gifs are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use web beacons on this site from time to time for this and other purposes. 

Cookies and web beacons shall be deemed to be information submitted by you to us. 

**Collection of Information by Third-Parties**

Our website may contain links to other websites whose information practices or policies may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

This website may offer content (e.g., contests or promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may have access to personally identifiable information that you may submit to participate in the site activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of such information. The site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will have access to such information. 

This website may use a third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see on a web page. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to facilitate such advertisements and their effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies. 

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

Access to Information 

Access to personally identifiable information that is submitted to our website may be accessible for a limited period of time from the point of submission. 

You may also send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or address requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, e-mail address and the password you use for said service. 

E-mail Administration   
info@rtilive.pk 

**For users under 18** If you are aged 18 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission before using this website and before submitting any information. 

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may contact us info@rtilive.pk 

**Updates & Effective Date**

We may update or amend this privacy policy from time to time. You are advised to review this policy each time you use this website. The Privacy Policy posted on this website was last updated/amended on September 20, 2010.
